Guide to the Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education (CIDDE), University of Pittsburgh, Photograph Collection, 1986-2005 UA.15.38.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education (CIDDE), University of Pittsburgh, Photograph Collection
1986-2005
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh. Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education
UA.15.38.1
10 Linear Feet (160 volumes containing approximately 634,000 negatives, 8,800 proof sheets and prints, 1,812 CDs of digital images, and 1 records center box)
The Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education (CIDDE) Photographic Services department provides the University of Pittsburgh community with support for its instruction, institutional, and research missions through location and studio photography. Photographs focus on special events, portraiture, general university buildings, student activities, public relations, sports and stock photography. Popular topics include the Chancellor, Pitt Football, Pitt Basketball, and high profile visitors. This collection consists of photographic negatives, 35mm slides, digital images, and contact sheets taken between 1986 and 2005.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of CIDDE in July 2014.
Arrangement
The content is arranged into three series within 160 archival binders as created by CIDDE. All items bear an assigned job number and accompanying job request slip. Scope and Contents Notes are included to provide context as to the topics covered in each series and subseries.
Series I. Photographer, 1988-2005
Series II. Unified Storage, 2002-2005
Series III. Stock Photographs, 1986-2001
History
Photography services at the University of Pittsburgh most likely existed as early as the late 1960s or early 1970s; however, no exact date is known for the establishment of an official department. The earliest information regarding the creation of a Photographic Services department dates to 1977. Prior to the formation of a singular department, two different University departments offered photographic services. One was the Communication Center located in G-20 Hillman Library whose photographers were located on the 9th floor of the Cathedral of Learning. This group was managed by Charles Hughes. The second group, known as Medical Media Services, was located in Scaife Hall. This group consisted of film makers and photographers notably; Pittsburgh photographer Herb Ferguson served as the manager.
Sometime in late 1977 or early 1978 the Communication Center and the Medical Media Services groups were combined to form the University Center for Instructional Resources (UCIR) under the direction of Dr. J. Fred Gage. The newly formed UCIR also had a graphics unit.
Effective July 1, 1995 UCIR merged with the University External Studies Program (UESP), the Technology and Evaluation Center of Academic Computing, and the Office of Faculty Development to form the University Center for Instructional Development & Distance Education (CIDDE). Also included were the learning laboratories of the Graduate School of Library Science. The goal was to facilitate learning and teaching processes through the provision of educational technology and resources. Photographic Services was relocated from Scaife Hall to its present location in the Information Sciences Building in the fall of 1989. In the mid to late 1990s Photographic Services began the transition from film to digital photography and began using digital cameras exclusively in the early 2000s. Digital photography has now completely superseded and replaced film-based photography at CIDDE.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection consists of photographs taken by the Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education (CIDDE) Photographic Services department whose mission is to provide the University of Pittsburgh community with support for its instruction, institutional, and research missions through location and studio photography. Photographs in this collection were taken between 1986 and 2005 and focus on activities of the Chancellor, special events, portraiture, high profile visitors, university buildings, student activities, public relations, sports and stock photography. The bulk of the collection contains 35mm negatives, 120mm negatives, 4x5 negatives, 35mm slides, proof sheets, contact prints, and CDs of digital photographs.
A searchable electronic inventory arranged by job number is available to archives staff to provide more in-depth searching of subjects. Information here duplicates what appears on the job slips.
Previous Citation
Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education (CIDDE), University of Pittsburgh, Photograph Collection, 1986-2005, UA.15.38.1, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Student activities -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; College presidents; Architecture -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Sports -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Oakland (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Photography -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Universities and colleges -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; University of Pittsburgh
- Photographer, 1986-2005; I.
  - Photographer: Kimberly Pasko, 1988-1997; 1.; (9 volumes)
    Scope and Content Notes
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Kimberly Pasko between December 1988 and January 1997. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Theatre, Sports, Awards, Guest Speakers, Check Presentations, Convocations, Receptions, Board of Trustees, Provost's Inaugural Lecture, Alumni Events, Graduations, Homecoming, Jewish Community Center, Duquesne Club, Fred Rogers, Bradford Campus, Titusville Campus, Semester at Sea, Speaker Series, Career Fair, Turkish Delegates, Lantern Night, and Dr. Thomas E. Starzl Lecture Series.
  - Photographer: Michelle Ray, 2001-2001; 2.; (2 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Michelle Ray between August 2001 and May 2002. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Sports, Jazz Concerts, Theatre, Board of Trustees, Alumni Events, Provost's Lecture Series, Science 2001, Pitt Day, Convocations, Move In Day, Media Day, Stock Photographs, Graduations, Orchestra, Dean's Day, Match Day, Legacy Laureate, and Robert Moore Symposium.
  - Photographer: Curtis Reeves, 1997; 3.; (1 volume)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Curtis Reeves between April 1997 and May 1997. The subjects covered include: Portraits, visiting speaker Salman Rushdie, Lectures, Theatre, Outsourcing Conference, Check Presentations, Scaife Hall Lecture Series, Alumni Dinner, Provost's Lecture Series, Engineering Research, IMDI Group.
  - Photographer: Sue Wrbican, 1991-1994; 4.; (5 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Sue Wrbican between September 1991 and July 1994. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Gordon Foundation Breakfast, Sports, Keg Roll, visiting speaker Nelson Mandela, IBM Ribbon Cutting, H.J. Heinz Company Foundation Fellows, ROTC Protest, Reception for August Wilson, Alumni Events, Reception for the Secretary to the Commonwealth, Graduations, Young Writers Workshop, Darlington Library, Howard Hughes Fellows, Titusville Campus, Parents Day, CAS 50th Reunion 1993, Semester at Sea, Schenley Cafe, Carnegie Science Center, Provost's Lecture Series, Architectural Shots, Object Shots, and Decades Studio Shots.
  - Photographer: Jim Krandel, 1989-1993; 5.; (2 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Jim Krandel between 1989 and 1993. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Check Presentations, Award Presentations, the Heinz Lecture Series with Henry Kissinger, Fulbright Professor, AT&T Computer Lab, Video Production and Control Room, and Dean Ferrerier Retirement.
  - Photographer: Patty Nagle, 1997-2002; 6.; (13 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken September 1997 and May 2002. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Theatre, Sports, Gamelan, Jazz Festival, Nationality Rooms, Provost Dinner, Foreign Dignitaries, Miracle of Miracles, Bike Fair, Dean's Retreat, Monte Carlo Night, Pitt Ambassadors, ROTC Ball, Chancellors Weekend, Convocations, Secretary of Labor, Black History Month Lecture, Falk Library Dedication, Conferences, Homecoming, Student Kickoff, Masonic Temple Tour, Simmons Symposium, President of Turkey, Dr. Thomas E. Starzl Lecture Series, Elmer H. Grimm Sr. Pharmacy Museum, Retirement Receptions, Drue Heinz Lecture Series, Mellon Hall Ribbon Cutting, Posvar Hall Dedication, Kennywood, Blue and Gold Ceremony, Same Sex Benefits Protest, 50th Reunion Dinner 1997, 50th Reunion Luncheon 2000, Fanfest, Discovery Weekend, Mayor of Macedonia, Mothman Diaries Set, White Coat Ceremony, Graduations, Student Day of Caring, and Petersen Event Center.
  - Photographer: Zsuzsi Matolcsy, 1990-1995; 7.; (1 volume)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Zsuzsi Matolcsy between December 1990 and April 1995. The subjects covered include: Board of Trustees, Graduations, Receptions, 50th Reunion 1992, Sports, Kwanzaa Celebration, Retirement Receptions, Alumni Events, Chancellor's Reception, Nationality Rooms, Founder's Day, Pitt Ambassadors, Bipolar Disorder Conference, Homecoming Brunch, and Martin Luther King Jr. Program.
  - Photographer: Koleen Mitchell, 2001-2002; 8.; (2 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Koleen Mitchell between March 2001 and May 2002. The subjects covered include: Fawcett Commons Dedication, Sports, Annual Board Meeting, Alumni Events, Debate, Commencements, Graduations, Awards, Retirement Receptions, Heinz Lecture Series, Day of Caring, Katz Leadership Conference, and the Annual Henry T. Bahnson Lecture.
  - Photographer: Mike Drazdsinski, 1997-2002; 9.; (11 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Mike Drazdsinski between May 1997 and May 2002. The subjects covered include: Stock Photographs, Southside Practice Field, Demolition of Pitt Stadium, Petersen Events Center Construction, Portraits, Senate Council Meeting, Dot Talley Center Ribbon Cutting, Sports, Partners in Progress, Day of Caring, Convocations, Theatre, Check Presentations, Broadhurst Science Center Dedication, Church Brew Works, Graduations, Alumni Events, Retiree Reception, Young Writers Workshop, Residence Life, Blue and Gold Society, Fireworks, Homecoming, Jazz Concert, Duquesne Club, Teplitz Memorial Moot Courtroom, Press Conference, Pitt Stadium, Team Pittsburgh, Media Day, Midnight Madness, Pep Rally, Women's Leadership Conference, Jazz Festival, Japanese Delegation, Bowl Game Press Conference, Bayer Distinguished Lecture Series, Light Up Night, Tangerine Bowl, Last Basketball Game at Fitzgerald Field House.
  - Photographer: Shawn Sullivan, 1993-1998; 10.; (4 volumes)
    This subseries is contains photographs taken by Shawn Sullivan between August 1993 and March 1998. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Lantern Night, Partners in Progress, visiting speaker Lord Geoffrey Howe, Lectures, Convocations, Teplitz Memorial Moot Courtroom, Blue and Gold Society, Jazz Seminar, Sports, Chancellor's Reception with Al Gore, Day of Caring, Classrooms, Check Presentations, White Coat Ceremony, Provost's Lecture Series, Gamelan, Titusville Campus, Dr. Thomas E. Starzl Lecture Series, Fred Rogers, and Alumni Events.
  - Photographer: Joe Kapelewski, 1998-2002; 11.; (11 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Joe Kapelewski between June 1998 and April 2002. The subjects covered include: Young Writers Workshop, Awards Banquet, White Coat Ceremony, Portraits, River Front Beautifying, Convocations, Sports, Gateway Clipper, Homecoming, Fireworks, Heinz Chapel Holiday Concert, Stock Photographs, the Annual Henry T. Bahnson Lecture, Alumni Events, Scope and Scalpel Society, Protesters, Heinz Chapel, Fanfest, Lantern Night, Prime Minister of Luxembourg, Forbes Demolition Site, Press Conference, Theatre, Dean's Day, United Way, Panther Hollow Stock Photographs, Media Day, Teaching Awards, Symposium of Energy in the Environment, Howard Hughes Fellows, Legacy Laureate, Pitt Carnegie Mellon University Joint News, Queen Mother Reception on the occasion of her visit, Teaching Times, Fawcett Commons Dedication, Mothman Diaries Set, Graduation, K. Leroy Irvis Reading Room Dedication, Chancellor Mark A. Nordenberg Lectureship, Cameos of Caring, Homecoming Reception, Donation of Record Collection to Jazz Archive, Stephen Hawking lecture.
  - Photographer: Joanne Bartone, 1997-2000; 12.; (6 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Joanne Bartone between October 1997 and August 2000. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Sports, Graduations, Lectures, Music for the Holiday, Theatre, Jazz Festival, Panther Pride, Dr. Rosemary Scully Lecture Series, Cathedral of Learning, Retirement Receptions, Dr. Thomas E. Starzl Lecture Series, Commencements, Annual Henry T. Bahnson Lecture, Elmer H. Grimm Sr. Pharmacy Museum, Bouquet Gardens Groundbreaking, Executive Women's Panel, Chancellor Mark Nordenberg Pledging to United Way, Jazz Workshop, Dedication of Digital Recording Studio, Lecture Series, Day of Caring, Move In Day, Young Writers Workshop, Nationality Rooms, Scouting for Food, North Ireland Women's Business Delegation, Alumni Events, Hunger Strikes, Blue and Gold Society, Scaife Hall Lecture Series, Convocations, visit by the Ambassador of Austria, Last Day at Pitt Stadium, visit by the Prime Minister of Luxembourg, Provost's Lecture Series, Energy Symposium.
  - Photographer: Jason Blair, 2005; 13.; (1 volume)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Jason Blair between May 2005 and August 2005. The subjects covered include: 1787 Society Lunch, Portraits, Alumni Events, Teaching Times, Digital Library, Falcon, Special Olympics, and H.J. Heinz Company Foundation Fellows.
  - Photographer: Shawn Brackbill, 1997; 14.; 0 volume (1 volume)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Shawn Brackbill in 1997. The subjects covered include: Jazz Festival and Stock Photographs.
  - Photographer: Jeff Cepull, 1993-1994; 15.; (1 volume)
    This subseries is made contains photographs taken by Jeff Cepull between July 1993 and May 1994. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Homecoming Reception, Awards Banquet, Nigerian Group, Sports, Blue and Gold Society, Rehabilitation Institute 90th Anniversary, and Classrooms.
  - Photographer: Dave McAnall, 2001-2002; 16.; (1 volume)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Dave McAnall between December 2001 and February 2002. The subjects covered include: Scholar Athlete Dinner, Public Health, and Women's Basketball.
  - Photographer: Jim Burke, 1989-2000; 17.; (29 volumes)
    This subseries contains photographs taken by Jim Burke between October 1989 and October 2000. The subjects covered include: Portraits, Sears Grant, Board of Trustees, Higher Education Conference, Convocations, Henry Kissinger and Wesley Posvar, Commencements, Reunion, Sports, Anti-war Protest, Soldiers and Sailors Memorial Hall, Greek Olympics, Dance Marathon, Henry John Heinz III Funeral, Scouting for Food, Syria Mosque, Keg Roll, Classrooms, Board of Trustees, Nelson Mandela, Match Day, Golden Panther Staff, Young Writers Workshop, Jazz, Falcon's Nest, Provost Candidates, Hillman Library, Bicycle Day, Masonic Hall, 427 Memorial, Homecoming, Fireworks, Toys for Tots, Founders Day, K. Leroy Irvis Papers Donation, Gamelan, Blizzard Photos, Nationality Rooms, Taiwan/China Protest, Mark Nordenberg Elected Chancellor, Joe DeNardo, Salman Rushdie, Graduations, Media Day, White Coat Ceremony, visit of the President of Macedonia, Blue and Gold Society, Martin Luther King Jr. Lecture Series, Day of Caring, Annual International Pittsburgh Coal Conference, Liberty Bowl, Scope and Scalpel Society, visit of the Prime Minister of Luxembourg, Continuing Education 50th Reunion 2000, visit of President George W. Bush, and Legacy Laureate Tour.
  - Photographer: Herb Ferguson, 1958-1996
    - Dean Donald Stone, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - GSPIA-501A Bruce Hall; Dean Donald Stone, July 23, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Jim Kehl, April 24, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Pitt Ambassador's Scholarship Students, April 2, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dedication of Sutherland Hall, September 2, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IMDI) Arab Program, September 1, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Men's and Women's swim team, September 8, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - African-American art show, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Pitt Ambassadors golf outing-Nevillewood, September 14, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "Hail to Pitt" sign on building-Dr. Tuchi, September 16, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Barb Yonkovitz, Heinz Fellow, September 16, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Rosemary Scully (Chair, Physical Therapy) retirement recognition, September 21, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Management Program for Executives (MPE), September 22, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Management Program for Executives, September 29-October 14, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - University Center for Social and Urban Research-Jo Ann Kurtvz, October 19, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Masters of Business Administration billboard on Bigelow Blvd., October 20, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Marous reception as Chair of the board, October 22, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ed Palascak, Business School undergraduate, October 23, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Men's basketball, October 27, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - British consul presentation-western European studies, November 10, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Women's basketball-freshmen, November 12, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Women's Studies 20th anniversary, November 20, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Van Pool-for display, December 8, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Van Pool awards luncheon, December 16, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Helen Rush honorary presentation in Braun Room, December 16, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - John Majors, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Engineering class, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Surgical residents, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Football, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Pitt vs. Syracuse homecoming game, Mike Ditka, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
    - Management Program for Executives, Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Tuchi Christmas Party, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Football team pictures, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Ed Palascak, Business School undergraduate, January 22-29, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Fred Hetzel, January 28, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - John Majors with trophies, February, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Management Program for Executives, Spring 1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Bob Reteshka, Japanese Ambassador, March 5, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Engineering Marous Lecture, Dr. Juran, March 24, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Dan Nagy, March 31, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Detre retirement party and dinner, April 15, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Pitt Ambassadors, Dick Cheney Speaker, April 22, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - European Business Conference, April 26, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Don Henderson, Provost, May 1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Burkhart Holzner, Director University Center for Interational Studies (UCIS), May 1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Counselling Center, May 27, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Emergency Medicine residents, June 21, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Jamie Mowat, July 1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Etched Glass "Roy Rogers" in the Cathedral, July 20, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Don Henderson retirement and reception, July 22, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Quest Program, July 23, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Westinghouse workshop, August 3, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Professors MAC project, August 4, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Rubbish behind business school, August 24, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Lantern night, August 25, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IMDI) Arabic group, September 1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Football, Pitt vs. Virginia Tech., September 11, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Majors show at Lincoln school, October 6, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Class of 1944-1945 reunion, October 14, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - GSPIA Coca-Cola Scholarship, Dolores Vojta, October 14, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Engineering class of 1943 reunion, October 14, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Alumni functions at homecoming football game, October 16, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Property management, October 26, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Race car at stadium, November 3, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Men's basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Women's basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Swimming and Diving, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Engineering class, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Dr. Dave Cleveland, (Manufacturing Assistance Center), February 11-March 1, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - John Majors, March 9, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Larry Eldridge, football memorbilia, March 10, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Najuma Fletcher, Women's track, March 18, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Coal Conference, September 17, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Ralph Willard, men's basketball coach, November 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Sports facilities, March 29, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Sports awards banquet, April 14, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IMDI) group, June 17, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Emergency medicine residents, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Majors family portrait, June 24, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Tim Karen Scholarship and Coach Majors, June 27, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Bidanda and bar code reader, July 7, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Impact program, July 7, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Cindy Wertz, July 11, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Health fair, July 19, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Oakridge University, July 18, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Larry Ellis, M.D., July 21, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Law reception, August 23, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Management Program for Executives, September 19, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Football equipment managers, August 29, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Engineering department chairs, August 31, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Survey Research Center phone bank, September 21, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bike fair, September 27, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - John Majors show, September 28, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Engineering biotech center labs, September 29, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Chang Benedict, International Management and Development Institute (IMDI), October 10, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Management Program for Executives, October 12, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Engineering homecoming reception dinner, class of 1944 and 1969, October 14, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Engineering homecoming, October 15, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Football, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Pitt vs. West Virginia University, homecoming, October 15, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Men's and women's gymnastics, October 21, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Cheerleaders, October 29, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Police bike patrol, November 3, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Law alumni dinner, November 5, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Larry Weber, November 9, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Pitt vs. Ohio University football, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Jazz Seminar, November 3, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Engineering commemorative plaque in lobby, November 11, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Men's basketball, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Frank Toker, December 2, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Engineering student councils, December 7, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Computer learning center, January 9, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 39)